psdschools.org 2006-06-20

# PSD Privacy Policy

Poudre School District is committed to ensuring the privacy of all our website users and the accuracy of all data within it.  As we strive to maintain the currency of all data contained within the website, no data within the website is guaranteed or deemed reliable. 

**Collection of Personal Information**  
The Poudre School District website does not collect personal information about individuals without their knowledge. Personal information may be requested when you engage in any of the following online activities: 

  * Register on our site to use services available only to registered users 
  * Use district email 
  * Submit information for content or editorial purposes, such as news items, letters of opinion, press releases 
  * Submit information to the site via a form. This includes activities such as contact form or request form 

**Use of Personal Information**  
Personal information submitted **will not** be transferred to any non-affiliated third parties unless otherwise stated at the time of collection.

When a user submits personally identifiable information it is used only for the purpose stated at the time of collection. No collected information is shared with any other party.

 **Anonymous Data and Cookies**  
While personal information is protected, we sometimes collect anonymous data about your computer's capabilities and/or your online browsing pattern. This information is used to improve the design of our website.

The Poudre School District website may place a small text file, called a "cookie", in the browser files of your computer. A cookie is used to track your session on the website as you traverse different pages. It is used by the server to differentiate you from another user. It is completely anonymous and does not contain any personal information about you. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being set. If you choose to not accept cookies, the website may not perform as expected.

 **Kids and Parents**  
The entire Poudre School District website is kid safe and contains no material that would be considered offensive or meant for adult users only. If you feel any portion of the website content is questionable please [contact us](http://www.psdschools.org/contact).

 **Log files**  
The District uses Internet Protocol ("IP") addresses to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. IP addresses are used to gather broad demographic information, such as a visitor's country, operating system, browser types, frequency of visit, and so on.

 **Security**  
Poudre School District takes reasonable precautions to protect your personal information. When you submit information via the website, it is protected both online and off-line. When personal information is required, that information is stored in a secure location on our server. This information is not accessible from the web.  All user information is restricted to authorized employees. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific task, for example, a Human Resources Job Specialist, are granted access to personal information. The server used to store personal information is kept in a secure environment behind a firewall.

 **Contact Information**  
If you have comments, questions, or concerns about our privacy policy please contact us in one of the following ways:

Send email to: [webmaster@psdschools.org](mailto:webmaster@psdschools.org)

Send postal mail to the following address:   
PSD Webmaster  
2413 LaPorte Ave  
Fort Collins, CO 80521
